http://www.thailand-golf-tours.com.au/privacy

DestinationsChinaMission Hills HaikouMission Hills Shenzhen
ThailandBangkokChiang MaiHua HinKanchanaburiKhao YaiPattayaPhuket
VietnamDalatDanangNha TrangSaigon
CambodiaPhnom PenhSiem Reap
Tour DatesInformationCaddiesCurrencyDo's and Dont'sThai WordsTerms and Conditions
Special OffersBook Now
Thailand Golf Tours
×
DestinationsTour DatesInformationCaddiesCurrencyDo's and Dont'sThai WordsTerms and ConditionsSpecial OffersBook Now
Personal information collection
We may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:
information about your use of this website;
information that you provide for the purpose of registering with the website;
information about transactions carried out over this website;
information you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
any other information that you send to us.
Using personal information
We may use your personal information to:
administer this website;
personalise the website for you;
enable your access to and use of the website services;
publish information about you on the website;
send to you products that you purchase;
supply to you services that you purchase;
send you statements and invoices;
collect payments from you; and
send you marketing communications.
Where we disclose your personal information to our agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Thailand Golf Tours may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
Securing your data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers.
Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.
Updating this statement
We may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
Other websites
This website may contains links to other websites.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please contact us.
NEED HELP?
Got a question? Are you looking for that golfing holiday of a lifetime? Then just give us a call or drop us a line for all your enquiries. Email info@thailandgolftours.com.au
0419 264 800
Send an enquiry
NEWSLETTER
Would you like to know whats happening at Thailand Golf Tours?
Subscribe to receive our newsletter.
Subscribe Now
Contact Us
0419 264 800
info@thailandgolftours.com.au
PO Box 303, Beecroft NSW 2119
Facebook
Twitter
Newsletter
About UsThailand Golf Tours started out in 1996 when two friends starting taking some of their friends to a great golfing destination, Thailand.
As the word spread about the amazing time that Thailand offered, the group numbers grew, now the group sizes average 40 - 100 golf fanatics from throughout the world, from Australia, New Zealand, South Africa, India, UK, Dubai, Singapore, Alaska & Korea (pretty much where ever you can hit a golf ball).
Copyright © 2018 Thailand Golf Tours  |  Powered by Kentico
Copyright
Disclaimer
Privacy
Sitemap
